## Erik J Stone

3933 N. Kerby Ave. Portland OR 97227 Email: spologas@gmail.com

**Phone:** (503) 757- 0415

Linkedin: www.linkedin.com/in/erik-stone-33b2a661

Github: https://github.com/Erik-jpg

#### **Brand Statement**

Using scientific methods, (such as reading, taking notes, forming hypotheses, and testing them), I experiment with technologies to learn the capabilities and limits of them and then apply that knowledge to the best of my understanding; While still discussing and researching new ideas.

#### **Technologies**

HTML, CSS,CSS Frameworks: Bulma and Bootstrap, JavaScript, APIs, Cookies, MySQL, Inquirer, Express, Mongo.

#### **Projects**

For a list of projects, please visit my portfolio page: https://erik-jpg.github.io/Erik-Stone-Portfolio/

#### **Education**

# **University of Oregon**

06/24/2021 to 10/28/2021

The U of O has put together a program of a Coding Boot Camp that was part of the Oregon Codes Job education. This six month long boot camp is designed for anyone with some knowledge of coding to join and learn how to become a "Full-Stack" Web Developers.

## **University of Phoenix**

05/2021 to present

University of Phoenix is based in Phoenix Arizona, and allows an online learning experience that matches all types of people. Currently I am in the pursuit of a bachelors in Writing.

# Portland Community College

2002 to 2004

After moving to Portland, once again I wanted to try some other college education. I was originally going for Liberal Arts and also took some Web Developer classes, this was my first introduction to coding and found that I enjoyed it. I still have my Dream Weaver CD and book somewhere...

## Kenai Peninsula College

1999 to 2001

After completing a G.E.D, graduating a year early, I began to explore options that would make for a career. After an initial dive into art as a bachelors degree, it had led me to believe that this was not for me.

### **Experience**

Interurban 08/17/2021 to Present

4057 N Mississippi Ave Portland OR 97227

Title: Kitchen Employee

Skills: Prioritizing my skills based on demand, supporting stations, communication with coworkers, attention to detail, applying new skills.

Shine Distillery

10/28/2019 to 06/08/2021

4232 N Williams Ave Portland OR 97227

Title: Line Cook, Pastry Chef

Skills: verbal and written communication with coworkers, conceptualized specials and new menu ideas, conducted research of new techniques, tools, and recipes, preparing food and deserts, ascertained the skills of new hires and trained them accordingly.

#### Hopworks Bike Bar

04/09/2018 to 10/28/2019

Title: Lead Line

Skills: verbal and written communication, systematized product, optimized processes, assisted my coworker's success, prioritized the next task based on demand.

Catalyte 04/09/2018

Coding boot camp to hire, a five month or twenty week, coding program where individuals are given tests: reading, writing, comprehension, math and logic puzzles. After the individual passes, they are invited to an interview. After the four months that same individual will be hired and sign a two year contract.

Broder Nord 06/05/2016 to 04/01/2012

3765 N Mississippi Ave Portland OR 97227

Skills: Communication even under duress, conceptualized new menu items, executed tasting menus, party menus, adjusted orders based on business, contacted providers, assisted coworkers with their menu ideas, implemented new processes for service and preparing food, assessed and provided aid to stations that needed assistance, revitalized the moral of the whole team, ascertained the skills of new hires and trained them accordingly.